

Ali Arjmand

DoB: 1991/4/25 Marital Status: Married Military Service: Non Medical Exempt

About

I'm Ali Arjmand, 29 years old, from Lorestan, started programming with HTML and CSS, and then I went to PHP and MySqI, and now I have specialized in them and done several projects in various fields. Interested in career advancement and learning specific skills.

Contact

arjmand08@yahoo.com



(+98)9108810098



Koohdasht, Lorestan

Skills

Office

Adobe Photoshop

PHP, Html, CSS

Mysql, SqlServer

VB.Net, VB6

Education

Master of Copmuter

Branch: Software

Institute/University: Payamnoor Tehran-Shomal

From 2020

Bachelor of Copmuter

Branch: Software

Institute/University: Isfahan University Jahad

2011 - 2014 GPA: 18.3

Associate of Copmuter

Branch: Software

Institute/University: Boroujerd Boys Technical and Vocational School

2009 - 2011 GPA: 16.26

Work Experiences

Computer User

Organization: Imam Khomeini Relief Committee

May 2008 - May 2009

Computer Expert

Organization: Kuhdasht city governorship

February 2015 - March 2011

Informatics Officer

University: JuyandeganElm

From July 2013

Languages

English



Listening Level



Writing Level



Speaking Level



Reading Level

(Laki (Mother Tongue



Listening Level



Writing Level



Speaking Level



Reading Level

Social Network



arjmand08

■ ICDL Seven Skills

Institute: Lorestan Technical and Vocational Center No. 3

Certificates

Date: October 2011

arjmand08

arjmand08

Projects

Website of Hekmat Giyah Health Services Complex

Date: March 2020

Link: https:hekmat-giah.ir